

AYUSHI J. VORA

- Self Employed
- Associate at SDA Legal, Ahmedabad

Cell: +91 8141889198

Email: ayushivoralegal@gmail.com

Education

 BBA-LLB (IPR Hons.), Institute of Law, Nirma University, Ahmedabad (CGPI -7.54)
2013 - 2018

Work Experience

- Associate at SDA Legal, Ahmedabad since December,2022.
- Individual Practice since January, 2022.
- Assistant Manager, Legal at Arvind SmartSpaces Ltd.
 April 2021 – December 2021
- Sr. Executive, Legal at Arvind SmartSpaces Ltd.

July 2019 - April 2021

H.K. Acharya & Co., Ahmedabad
June 2018 – June 2019

Certificate Courses

- Harvard US-India Initiative 2017
- Arbitration & Mediation Training Workshop by AMLED

Additional Skills

- Well versed with Microsoft Office
- Fluent in English language
- Research and Drafting Skills

Background

Ayushi graduated from Institute of Law, Nirma University with a degree in BBA-LLB (IPR hons.) in April 2018. She is currently working for individual clients and is also associated with SDA Legal, Ahmedabad expanding her scope of practice to Real Estate Transactions along with Contractual and corporate law practice. She has also gained experience on handling legal dilemmas faced by Corporates during her term of service as an Assistant Manager at Arvind SmartSpaces Ltd. This has helped her gain understanding of the RERA and other land related regulations. She has also been exposed to the funding side involved in real estate transactions from the Builder's perspective. She has been actively involved in Company audit practices and during her term at Arvind, she was promoted in a short span of time of her joining. She has prior experience working with the litigation team at H.K. Acharya & Co. that has helped her explore the facet of IP Laws and is well acquainted with the court procedure along with drafting and research work. She has done varied internships concerning different areas of the Law. Her prior work experience is complemented by sound drafting and qualitative research skills.

Career Objective

Gain experience in the field of Civil & Company laws vis-à-vis and leverage her knowledge and to add value to the organization she is committed to.

Professional Experience

SDA Legal, Ahmedabad

Handling an all-inclusive legal functioning and working for various renowned organizations such as Arvind Limited, Arvind SmartSpaces Ltd., ATIRA, Kiara Space Ventures etc. along with various individual clients. Giving them access to multi-faceted legal solutions that ranges from drafting legal notices, vetting service contracts, carrying out Title search and providing Title reports, resolving Title queries with Buyers/ Banks, drafting Agreements such as Technology Transfer Agreement, Supplementary Agreement, Articles of Agreement, ATS, Sale Deed, Ancillary Agreements to ATS, Terms and Conditions for Work Orders etc. As an associate, my role is to provide a multi-faceted response to all types of legal queries.

Arvind SmartSpaces Ltd. (Real Estate Company)

Positions: Senior Executive, Legal - Assistant Manager, Legal

- Drafting, reviewing and vetting Agreements to Sell, Sale Deed, POA, Tripartite Agreements, Third Party Contracts and Bank related documents
- RERA Quarterly submission and resolving queries raised during RERA registration.
- Resolving Audit related queries and supporting with appropriate legal stance.
- Assisting in legal documentation for customer related notices and litigation matters.
- Engaging in conference calls from Builder's side with the Bank and customer to resolve funding/loan queries.
- Briefing counsels for litigation matters or title related queries.
- Taking part in Business Development Conferences and supplementing company structural decisions with appropriate legal opinion.
- Submitting responses to GST Department explaining Tax liabilities.
- Assisting in TDR transactions.

H.K. Acharya & Co., Ahmedabad (IPR Firm)

- Drafting Notices, Reply Applications, Rejoinders, Suit and research on Ongoing Cases.
- Preparing Case Synopsis and Written Submissions.
- Mentioning at City Civil Court and High Court.

Prior Internship Experience

- K. Nanavati & Gandhi Associates, Ahmedabad IPR Practice and Trial Courts Internship
- Universal Legal Ahmedabad IPR Firm Internship
- Jani & Co., Ahmedabad Firm Internship (Real Estate Laws)
- Tax Law Consultancy, Mumbai Firm Internship (Laws relating to Customs and Excise Duties)
- Shirish Tolia (Retd. District & Sessions Court Judge, Advocate Gujarat High Court) & Parth Tolia (Advocate, Gujarat High Court)- (Laws in relation to CRPC and IPC)
- Thakorbhai M Patel & Associates, Ahmedabad Firm Internship (Laws in relation to CRPC and IPC)

Projects (Research Papers & Articles) undertaken at University Level

- Intellectual Property Rights Ambush Marketing A Risk to corporate sponsorship?
- Intellectual Property Rights Comparative Advertising and its relation with Trademark Infringement
- Contract Law Agreements in Restraint of Trade Void
- Corporate Law Insider Trading in Companies
- Women & Law- Risky Lifestyle & Offences against Women